#### **Justin Hopkins**

9238 W Ontario Dr Littleton, CO 80128 justinhopk@gmail.com ◊ (214) 235-9437

Data Analyst and SharePoint Developer with 13+ years of experience in application development and data interpretation to drive business solutions. Expert knowledge in programming, technical writing, and analytics. Excellent understanding of business processes and tools for effective data analysis and automation.

## Work Experience

# OmniCell/PSG 340B; Plano, TX

Quality Analyst II, June 2019-Present

- Lead a team of 4 to prioritize issues and communicate to leadership
- Implemented new clients into data ingestion and processing structures
- Performed trending analysis to proactively identify data

### Mr. Cooper; Irving, TX

Business Analyst II, May 2017 – June 2019

- Developed a Mail Merge application for letters and documents to be prepped for printing and mailing
- Created SSIS packages for the automatic ingestion of data from 3<sup>rd</sup> party partners
- · Created and lead training classes for new document tracking software

#### JP Morgan Chase; Lewisville, TX

Information Analyst II; Nov 2009 – May 2017

- Built a SharePoint Application to provide Quality Analysts an area to perform reviews, and automated data ingestion
- Developed a SharePoint Application that tracked and reported on Compliance Officer's tasks
- Created SSRS dashboard reporting on process flows
- Produced reporting for Management via SQL/Excel

# Education

### University of Texas at Dallas; Richardson, TX

BA Literary Studies, May 2009

# Other Qualifications

- 13 Years experience in SQL, SSIS, SSRS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, VB, and JAVA
- Expert in all Office 365 applications
- Experience in Project Management and Leadership
- Strong analytical and quantitative skills
- Experience in creating and leading training on applications and workflows

# **References Available Upon Request**